Hi, I'm Jay French at jayfrenchstudios.com, and I'm going to show you how to draw clasped hands.
Okay, to draw clasped hands, of course there are many angles you can do this from, we're going to do it from pretty much the forward angle like this, so, what you have is, I'm going to draw the back of the hands.
We have your basic wedge of a hand, give the impression of that, but, and I've done them too far apart, so, we want them clasped tight so let's do this.
Start with your thumbs and draw the thumb that's going to go over the top first.
And one underneath second, and from here you would think you would just be drawing something like this.
But it doesn't work that way because they overlap, so draw your top finger again, and it's going to be the same hand, if you clasp your own fingers you'll notice this.
It's going to be the same hand that has the thumb on top.
It's your top finger in there.
Now you have a smaller, because it's half covered by the other hand, ring finger, or index finger from that hand.
And the same thing is happening here, it's half covered until it comes out here.
And that's how to do the clasped hand from that angle until you see just the hint of the pinkie finger there.
Then show your knuckle line, from there you can add shading.
Fingernails.
And, you have the front view of clasped hands.
And that is one way to draw clasped hands.
Remember to look for photo sources as your best bet.